Michael Longley papers, 1960-2000
Emory University
- Edna Longley papers, 1962-2000, Series 11; Boxes 78-80
  - John Hewitt Summer School records, circa 1966-1996, Subseries 11.2; Box 80
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Petition, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Printed material, 1988 - 1995 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Printed material, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Parodic poems re. JHSS, circa 1966 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 80, Folder 12)
Index of Selected Correspondents
This index, which relates to the correspondence in Series 1, covers letters only up to 1992.
Adcock, Fleur 1975 August 7, TLS [in verse], 1 p. 1975 November 25, ALS, 2 pp. 1976 July 24, ALS, 2 pp. 1978 March 22, ALS, 2 pp. 1979 February 20, ALS, 1 p. 1979 August 24, ALS, 1 p. 1979 September 2, ALS, 2 pp. 1980 January 10, ALS, 2 pp. w/ enclosure ["Hotspur," 5 pp.; and "Shakespeare's Hotspur," 1 p.] 1980 February 16, ALS, 2 pp. 1980 February 23, ALS, 2 pp. w/ enclosure ["Eclipse," 1 p.] 1981 May 1, ALS, 2 pp. w/ enclosure ["The High Tree," 3 pp.; "Tunbridge Wells," 1 p.; "Lantern-Slides," 2 pp.; and "Scalford Again," 1 p.] 1981 July 23, ALS, 2 pp. 1981 August 27, ALS, 1 p. 1981 September 17, ALS, 2 pp. 1981 October 27, ACS 1981 December 27, ALS, 2 pp. 1982 February 11, ALS, 3 pp. 1982 March 29, ALS, 2 pp. 1982 July 25, ALS, 2 pp. 1983 May 23, ALS, 2 pp. 1984 May 3, ALS, 1 pp. 1984 May 16, ALS, 2 pp. 1984 July 10, ALS, 1 p. 1985 January 26, ALS, 2 pp. 1985 October 24, ACS 1986 April 14, ACS 1986 August 30, ALS, 1 p. 1988 July 26, ACS 1988 October 20, ACS 1989 December 23, TLS, 2 pp. 1990 September 7, TLS, 2 pp. [n.d.], ACS
Amis, Martin 1978 May 5, TLS, 1 p.
Betjeman, John 1976 August 4, ALS, 2 pp.
Boland, Eavan 1964 December 15, TLS, 1 p. 1965 January 30, ALS, 10 pp. 1965 February 6, ALS, 3 pp. 1965 March 8, ALS, 3 pp. 1965 May 13, ALS, 1 p. 1965 May 20, ALS, 6 p. [1965 May?], ALS, 1 p. [1965?], ANS, 1 p. 1966 January 8, ALS, 1 p. 1966 March 25, ALS, 2 pp. 1966 October 15, ALS, 6 pp. 1967 May 16, ALS, 1 p. [1967?], ANS, 1 p. 1973 January 29, ALS, 3 pp. [n.d.], ALS, 1 p.
Carson, Ciaran 1977 March 16, ACS 1978 August, ACS 1984 May, ACS 1985 July 22, ACS
Dunn, Douglas 1972 June 15, TLS, 3 pp. w/ enclosures ["Spring: No Spring," 1 p.; "Landing at Belfast," 1 p.] 1972 July 25, TLS, 1 p. 1972 December 8, TLS, 2 pp. 1973 April 11, TLS, 2 pp. 1973 April 18, TLS, 2 pp. 1973 April 27, TLS, 2 pp. 1974 February 27, TLS, 2 pp. [1974?], ACS 1975 April 6, TLS, 2 pp. 1976 September 9, TLS, 3 pp. 1976 September 29, ALS, 1 p. 1977 September 22, TLS, 1 p. 1977 October 9, ALS, 1 p. 1977 October 11, ALS, 1 p. 1978 January 9, ALS, 1 p. 1978 August 30, TLS, 1 p. 1978 September 6, ANS, 1 p. w/ enclosure ["John Wilson in Greenock," 8 pp.] 1979 June 2, ALS, 1 p. 1981 January 19, TLS, 2 pp. w/ enclosures ["Shaving a Beard," 2 pp.; "Re-Reading Katherine Mansfield's.. .," 1 p.] 1981 October 13, ALS, 1 p. 1982 February 1, ALS, 1 p. 1982 June 14, ALS, 1 p. 1983 May 22, ALS, 1 p. 1984 January 23, ALS, 1 p. 1984 May 11, TLS, 1 p. 1984 July 16, TLS, 2 pp. 1985 February 26, ALS, 1 p. 1985 May 8, TLS, 1 p. w/ enclosure ["The Irish Swans," 1 p.] 1985 November 22, ANS, 1 p. 1986 February 10, TLS, 2 pp. 1986 March 18, ALS, 2 pp. 1986 March 6, TLS, 1 p. 1986 March 31, TLS, 1 p. 1986 April 29, ALS, 2 pp. 1987 January 7, ALS, 1 p. 1988 July 14, ALS, 1 p.
Durcan, Paul 1985 May 7, ACS 1987 October 14, ACS 1989 August, ACS 1991 May 18, ALS, 2 pp. 1991 November 8, ACS 1991 December, ACS 1992 January 1, ACS [n.d.], ALS, 1 p.
Ewart, Gavin 1973 July 19, ALS, 1 p. 1974 April 3, ALS, 1 p. 1974 July 7, ALS, 1 p. 1977 January 28, TLS, 1 p. 1977 February 5, ALS, 1 p. 1980 January 26, ACS 1985 February 11, ACS
Friel, Brian 1977 October 17, TLS, 1 p. 1980 May 26, ACS 1980 October 10, ALS, 2 pp. 1984 December 23, ALS, 2 pp. 1985 February 28, ALS, 1 p. 1992 April 15, ACS [n.y.] January 21, ACS [n.y.] June 4, ALS, 1 p. [n.y.] August 17, ALS, 2 pp. [n.y.] October 21, ALS, 1 p. [n.y.] December 10, ALS, 1 p. [n.d.], ACS
Fussell, Paul 1974 October 16, TLS, 1 p. 1983 May 25, TLS, 1 p.
Gallagher, Tess 1977 January 8, ALS, 4 pp. 1982 April 25, TLS, 2 pp. 1986 January 5, ACS
Hall, Donald 1989 November 30, TLS, 1 p. 1990 June 8, TLS, 1 p. 1990 August 23, TLS, 1 p.
Heaney, Marie 1976 October 13, ALS, 3 pp.
Heaney, Seamus [RESTRICTED] 1969 July 30, TLS, 2 pp. 1970 September 22, TLS, 1 p. 1971 April 26, TLS, 2 pp. 1971 June 14, ALS, 2 pp. 1973 May 16, TLS, 1 p. 1975 June 17, ALS, 3 pp. 1975 October 23, ACS 1975 November 13, ACS [1975?], ACS [signed "R. Lowell"] 1976 March 13, ACS 1976 September 26, ALS, 4 pp. 1977 November 15, ALS, 2 pp. 1978 January 4, ALS, 2 pp. 1978 April 18, ALS, 1 p. 1978 May 24, ALS, 2 pp. 1979 September 10, ACS 1979 November 26, ALS, 1 p. 1980 March 19, ALS, 1 p. 1980 June 19, ALS, 2 pp. [circa 1981 February], TLS, 2 pp. w/ enclosure ["The Railway Children," 1 p.] 1982 February 24, ACS 1982 May 24, ACS 1982 November 16, ACS 1983 May 7, ACS 1983 August 18, ACS 1983 October 3, ALS, 2 pp. 1984 April, ACS 1984 June 4, ACS 1984 June 25, ALS, 1 p. 1985 July 16, ALS, 2 pp. w/ enclosure ["A Quick Note," 1 p.] 1986 July 28, ACS 1987 July 20, ALS, 2 pp. 1987 August 17, ACS 1988 October 13, ALS, 4 pp. [1988?], ALS, 2 pp. 1989 March 30, ACS 1989 April 7, ACS 1989 September 5, ACS 1990 August 21, ALS, 1 p. 1991 March 11, ACS [n.y.] March 26, ACS [n.d.], TLS, 2 pp. [n.d.], ANS, 1 p. [n.d.], ACS [n.d.], ACS [n.d.], ACS [n.d.], ACS [n.d.], ACS
Hewitt, John 1976 MAR 12, telegram
Higgins, Aidan 1980 August 5, TLS, 1 p. 1985 August 23, TLS, 1 p.
Hobsbaum, Philip 1966 July 5, ALS, 1 p. 1966 December 28, ALS, 1 p. 1969 November 15, ALS, 2 pp. 1977 July 25, ACS 1980 January 21, ALS, 2 pp. 1985 February 24, TLS, 3 pp. [n.d.], ALS, 2 pp.
Hughes, Ted 1981 December 28, ALS, 1 p.
Johnston, Jennifer 1984 April 22, ACS 1984 August 24, ANS, 1 p. [1989?] January 27, ALS, 2 pp. [n.d.], ACS [n.d.], ACS
Kavanagh, Paul 1984 June 7, ACS 1984 October 9, ACS
Kennelly, Brendan 1973 November 23, TLS, 1 p. 1980 August 18, ALS, 3 pp. 1990 October 2, ALS, 2 pp.
Lowell, Robert 1976 July 12, TLS, 1 p.
McGuckian, Medbh 1979 July 9, ALS, 2 pp. 1985 April 18, ACS [1986?], ALS, 4 pp. [1987?] August 17, ALS, 2 pp. 1989 June 29, ALS, 2 pp. 1989, ALS, 2 pp. [1992?], ALS, 1 p. [n.y.] June 25, ALS, 1 p. [n.y.] July 24, ALS, 1 p. [n.y.] October 17, ALS, 2 pp. [n.y.] September 27, ACS
Mahon, Derek 1965 June 8, telegram 1966 January 6, ACS [1965 November], TLS, 2 pp. [circa 1966 December], TLS, 7 pp. [circa 1966], TLS, 1 p. [circa 1966], TLS, 3 pp. 1967 January 26, ACS 1967 January, ACS [circa 1967 January], TLS, 2 pp. [circa 1967 January], TLS, 4 pp. w/ enclosure [clipping] 1967 April 20, telegram 1971 December 7, TL [carbon], 1 p. [1971 December], TLS, 4 pp. 1977 February 14, ACS 1977 March 9, ALS, 1 p. 1978 March 7, ANS 1978 May 23, TLS, 1 p. w/ enclosures ["Father-in-Law," 1 p.; "The Old Snaps," 1 p.] 1978 August 27, ACS [circa 1978], ANS w/ enclosure ["The Sea in Winter," 6 pp.] [1979 May 22, TLS, 1 p. 1979 May 30, ANS w/ enclosure ["The Poet in Residence," 4 pp.] 1980 May 6, ACS 1980 June 10, ACS 1980 June 25, TLS, 1 p. w/ enclosure ["Courtyards in Delft," 1 p.] 1980 November 21, ACS 1980 November 17, ACS 1980 December 3, ACS 1981 June 28, TLS, 1 p. w/ enclosures ["Morning Radio," 1 p.; "A Bottle of Jameson," 2 pp.; "Another Sunday Morning," 2 pp.] 1981 August 28, TLS, 1 p. w/ enclosures ["Coca-Cola," 1 p.; "The Joycentenary Ode," 4 pp.; "One of these Nights," 2 pp.; "A Garage in Co. Cork," 2 pp.] 1981 September 3, TLS, 1 p. w/ enclosure ["One of These Nights," 2 pp.] 1981 October 15, TLS, 1 p. 1983 March 17, ANS w/ enclosures ["Night Drive," 1 p.; "Antarctica," 1 p.] 1983 April 21, ACS 1984 February 9, ACS 1986 June 9, ACS 1986 June 20, ACS 1991 April 22, ACS
Montague, John 1973 February 7, TLS, 1 p. 1976 January 6, ALS, 2 pp. 1976 January 29, ALS, 1 p. 1977 December, ACS 1980 January 20, ANS [postscript to letter from Evelyn Montague] 1980 May, ALS, 1 p. 1980 May, ALS, 2 pp. 1982 July 19, ALS, 2 pp. 1985 February 11, ACS [n.d.], TLS, 2 pp. [n.d.], ANS [n.d.], ACS [n.d.], ACS
Muldoon, Paul 1976 November 4, ALS, 1 p. 1981 March 16, ACS 1983 July 6, ACS 1984 September 8, ACS 1986 April 11, ACS 1986 August 18, ALS, 1 p. [1989?], ALS, 2 pp. 1990 January 5, ALS, 2 pp. [1991], ACS [n.y.] August 13, ALS, 2 pp. [n.d.], ALS, 1 p. [n.d.], ALS, 2 pp. [n.d.], ALS, 1 p. [n.d.], ALS, 1 p. [n.d.], ANS
Ní Dhomhnaill, Nuala 1986 March 5, ALS, 11 pp. 1986 July 8, ALS, 2 pp. 1986 May 15, ALS, 4 pp. 1986 December 11, ALS, 4 pp. 1987 January 17, ALS, 2 pp. 1989 May 4, ALS, 1 p. w/ enclosures ["Ruga de Chuid Na N-Amaiseach," 1 p.; "'crib' of Blodewedd," 1 p.] 1992 January 22, ACS [1992?], ACS [1992?], ACS [n.d.], ANS
Ormsbry, Frank 1978 July 27, TLS, 1 p. 1978 August 13, TLS, 1 p. 1981 September 29, ALS, 1 p. 1987 February 27, ALS, 1 p. [n.d.], ACS
Pinter, Harold [1973] August 13, ALS, 1 p.
Raine, Craig = 1978 March 5, ACS 1979 June 6, ACS 1980 September 12, ACS 1981 March 2, ACS w/ enclosure ["Grab First, Then Airfix," 1 p.] 1981 July 14, ACS 1981 October 10, ACS [1984?], ANS 1987 November 4, TLS, 1 p. 1988 January 7, TL [carbon], 1 p. 1988 February 3, ALS, 1 p. 1988 September 6, ACS 1988 December 20, ALS, 2 pp. 1989 May 10, ACS [n.d.], ANS
Simmons, James [circa 1971], TLS, 1 p. [circa 1973], ACS 1974 April 10, TLS, 2 pp. 1974 June 7, TLS, 1 p. 1974 August, ACS 1974 September 18, TLS, 1 p. 1975 December 15, TLS, 1 p. 1978 January 10, TLS, 1 p. 1978 February 28, TLS, 1 p. 1979 February 22, TLS, 1 p. 1983 January 26, TLS, 2 pp. w/ enclosure ["The Harvest is Past?"] 1983 March 30, TLS, 1 p. 1983 October 18, TLS, 1 p. 1985 April 27, TLS, 1 p. 1988 August 9, TLS, 1 p.
Stallworthy, Jon 1977 July 19, TLS, 1 p. 1981 February 23, TLS, 1 p. 1988 March 14, TLS, 1 p.
Stevenson, Anne [1976?], October 30, TLS, 1 p. 1976 November 24, TLS, 2 pp. 1976 December 13, TLS, 1 p. 1977 February 25, ACS
Thwaite, Anthony 1971 October 28, TLS, 1 p. 1972 September 26, TLS, 1 p. 1973 March 23, TLS, 2 pp. 1973 May 5, TLS, 1 p. 1973 August 17, TLS, 2 pp. 1973 September 6, TLS, 2 pp. 1974 February 2, ALS, 2 pp. 1974 May 13, TLS, 1 p. 1976 May 19, ACS 1976 October 22, ALS, 1 p. 1977 November 17, TLS, 1 p. 1978 January 23, TLS, 2 pp. 1978 August 29, TLS, 2 pp. 1978 October 31, TLS, 2 pp. 1979 June 21, TLS, 2 pp. 1980 May 19, TLS, 1 p. 1983 February 7, TLS, 1 p. 1983 February 17, ACS
Trevor, William [n.d.], ACS